Mr. Daniel
Your last batch of frogs was excellent
The female ones were all over 150 grams
Make sure you reserve this batch for me
No problem
But the price
As long as the quality stays the same
money is no object
I'll even take it at 500 per half kilo
Sis
Lewes
Uncle, Aunt
You're finally here
Please, have a seat
In-laws
You guys are dressed so
plainly
At our age
whether we live well
all depends on our kids
My daughter married your Lewes
So I don't expect much
Luckily, Daniel is successful and filial
He even insisted on buying me gold jewelry
Just this bracelet alone
cost 88,000
Nearly ten thousand for a bracelet
The whole set must be worth hundreds of thousands
Not just in the village
even in town
no one has it better than you
As the saying goes
when a son succeeds
his parents hold their heads high
Sandra, Samson
From now on, in this whole area
everyone will have to look up to
you two
Landon, Laura
Am I right
Yeah
Daniel is impressive
Lewes
Why don't you buy your parents and
Cynthia some better clothes
Even the poorest relief households in the village
dress better than you
What's going on
So lively
They're saying I raised a great son
Successful and filial
Daniel
Now that you've made it
help your brother-in-law too
At least get him some decent clothes
Don't embarrass us
Don't worry, Dad
Everyone knows
I'm generous
I never mistreat those who work for me
200,000
It's definitely for you
Daniel still remembers your kindness
Did I misjudge him
Please welcome my biggest supporter
Zane, come on